The final area to massage for a dog with, especially with problems with the front legs is going to be the side of the face, between the eye and the jaw.
Again, this may be an area that a dog will object to.
Some dogs will really like it.
If your dog will allow you to do it, those cheek muscles right between the eye and the bottom of the jaw, just a nice circular motion.
You want to be a little bit more gentle in this area than you've been on the back.
There's not as thick a muscle, and this is a good, relaxing pain relieving; particularly works down the front legs.
It's a continuation of one of those nice front leg meridians.
So again, you're going to do the same on the other side.
If the dog is nice and relaxed and quiet you can do both cheeks at once, and you're just going to do a nice broad fingertip or palm of the hand circular motion, and just relax that whole area.
This is one; again, if your dog is really not up for, or really doesn't want their face rubbed, don't worry about it.
You get them used to it over time work them into it.
Just get them used to a little bit of face touching, and then as they get calmer, you can do a little bit more, and a little bit more.